let questions = [
    {
        numb:1,
        question:"What is the primary male sex hormone?",
        answer:"C. Testosterone",
        options:[
            "A. Estrogen",
            "B. Progesterone", 
            "C. Testosterone", 
            "D. Prolactin"

        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:2,
        question:"Where are sperm produced in the male reproductive system",
        answer:"A. Testes",
        options:[
            "A. Testes", 
            "C. Epididymis", 
            "C. Vas Deferens", 
            "D. Urethra"
            
        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:3,
        question:"What is the function of the prostate gland?",
        answer:"C. Produces semen",
        options:[
            "A. Produces sperm",
            "B. Produces testosterone", 
            "C. Produces semen", 
            "D. Produces urine"
            
        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:4,
        question:"What is the tube that carries sperm from the testes to the urethra?",
        answer:"B. Vas Deferens",
        options:[
            "A. Epididymis", 
            "B. Vas Deferens", 
            "C. Seminal Vesicle", 
            "D. Bulbourethral Gland"
        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:5,
        question:"What is the external male reproductive organ?",
        answer:"A. Penis",
        options:[
            "A. Penis", 
            "B. Scrotum", 
            "C. Prostate Gland", 
            "D. Seminal Vesicle"
        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:6,
        question:"Which one of the following is not part of the male reproductive system?",
        answer:"B. Bladder",
        options:[
            "A. Scrotum",
            "B. Bladder",
            "C. Prostrate gland",
            "D. Penis",
        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:7,
        question:"A major male sex organ that produces and stores sperm.",
        answer:"B. Testicle",
        options:[
            
            "A. Prostate",
            "B. Testicle",
            "C. Ovary",           
            "D. Scrotum",
                
        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:8,
        question:"A set of coiled tubes that connect to the vas deferens.",
        answer:"B. Epididymis",
        options:[
            
            "A. Fallopian tubes",
            "B. Epididymis",
            "C. Urethra",
            "D. Prostate",
        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question:"A muscular tube that transports sperm-filled semen.",
        answer:"C. Vas deferens",
        options:[
            
            "A. Vagina",
            "B. Fallopian tube",
            "C. Vas deferens",
            "D. Pubic bone",
        ]
        
    },

    {
        numb:10,
        question:"The sac that holds the testes.",
        answer:"A. Scrotum",
        options:[
            "A. Scrotum",
            "B. Placenta",
            "C. Vas deferens",
            "D. Testis",
        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:11,
        question:"A process in which sperm-laden semen leaves the male body.",
        answer:"C. Ejaculation",
        options:[
            "A. Ovulation",
            "B. Gestation",
            "C. Ejaculation",
            "D. Urination",
        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:12,
        question:"A gland that makes some of the parts of semen.",
        answer:"C. Prostate",
        options:[
            "A. Ovary",
            "B. Scrotum",
            "C. Prostate",
            "D. Bulbourethral",
        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:13,
        question:"Where does sperm maturation occur",
        answer:"B. Epididymis",
        options:[
            "A. Seminiferous tubules",
            "B. Epididymis",
            "C. Prostate gland",
            "D. Bulbourethral gland",
        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:14,
        question:"Which gland produces a fluid that nourishes and protects sperm",
        answer:"B. Seminal vesicles",
        options:[
            "A. Prostate gland",
            "B. Seminal vesicles",
            "C. Bulbourethral gland",
            "D. Cowper's gland",
        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:15,
        question:"Which structure surrounds the urethra and produces an alkaline fluid",
        answer:"A. Prostate gland",
        options:[
            "A. Prostate gland",
            "B. Seminal vesicles",
            "C. Bulbourethral gland",
            "D. Epididymis",
        ]
        
    },
    
];